email-unlimited.com 2017-06-25

# Privacy Policy

Live Software Inc. ("Live Software") aims at providing you highly secure experience and it means taking your privacy very seriously. Privacy policy explains how we use personal information, got at this website. Please pay attention to the below information and find more about our privacy policy. 

## **What this Privacy Policy is about**

The policy describes how Live Software uses personal information which was received and collected by Live Software on http://www.email-unlimited.com, including information about your past use of Live Software products. Personal information is considered to be information about you. It is personally recognized like your first name, physical address, email, last name, and which isn’t alternatively publicly available.

This policy does **not** apply to the services of companies that Live Software does not control or own or to people that Live Software does not manage.

## **Information Collection and Use**

### **General**

Live Software gets personal information when you use Live Software subscription products or services, and when you visit certain Live Software pages. 

As soon as you register with Live Software and choose our services, you are not anonymous to us anymore. We use the information you provide us with to offer you a more professional attitude.

The information Live Software gets, is used for the following aims: to process your requests for products, to customize the content and advertisement you see on the website, improve our software, contact you, and conduct research.

### **Information Sharing and Disclosure**

Live Software does not sell and/or share your personal information with other individuals or nonaffiliated organizations and companies, besides providing products or services you've requested, when we have your permission, or under the following circumstances:

We suppose that it is necessary to exchange information in order to discourage, investigate, or employ measures regarding unauthorized activities, and violations of Live Software Terms of Use.

### **Cookies**

Live Software reserves the right to configure and access Live Software cookies on your PC.

 Live Software will have access to Live Software cookies previously kept on your computer when on our network of web sites in order to provide you with the best most customized experience.

### **Confidentiality and Security**

Ultra-secure data centers, where the Live Software’s personal servers are located, are tracked 24/7 by circuit video cams and security guards. Only specially authorized representatives may access the servers.

### **Changes to this Privacy Policy**

Live Software reserve the right to update this privacy policy. General updates will be performed with prominent notice on our website.

### **Suggestions and Questions**

Live Software values the chance of cooperation with you! If you have any suggestions or questions about our software, please feel free to contact us via email by clicking here. 

Last modified: November 1, 2012
